翻译｜0x7363@gmail.com
版本｜201301231408
字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
海绵电影公司呈献
Presented by SPONGE
在哪呢？
Where's that?
在去岑春的路上
A SPONGE and bom Film Produtions production Somewhere on the way to Choon-chun.
她的地刚买了就翻了一番
Her land doubled in price right after she bought it.
现在每英亩值七十万
It's now worth $700 an acre.
她挣了多少？
How much did she make?
她四十万一英亩买的，所以差不多挣了三千万
She bought it at $400 per acre. So probably around $30,000.
三千万？
$30,000?
- 哇  - 挣得真容易呀
- Wow.  - Easy money.
这些天她不容易联系上，她不接我电话
She's hard to reach these days. Won't take my calls.
你在哪呢？
Where are you?
你为什么不打个电话？我们一直在外边等着呢
Why didn't you call? We were waiting outside.
嗯
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
哪一层？
What floor?
好的
Okay.
现在投资地产太晚了吧？
Think it's too late for a stab at that?
你是在问我吗？
You're asking me?
或许不晚，既然都能翻一倍
Maybe not, since it already doubled.
不是谁都能买地赚钱的
Not everyone can make money on buying land.
我应该问问她吗？
Should I try asking her?
我告诉你了，她甚至都不接电话
I told you, she's not even taking calls.
为什么？
Why?
或许她不想请我喝饮料吧
Maybe she's trying to avoid buying drinks.
她以前也没请过
She never bought drinks even before.
去哪？
Where to?
我们应该吃点什么？
What should we eat?
这附近没什么吃的
There's nothing to eat around here.
- 你想吃什么？ - 我？
- What do you want?  - Me?
- 你要吃什么？ - 能快点吃完的就成
- What are you eating?  - Anything fast.
- 我需要更多时间来分析  - 那好像也没用呀
- I need more analyzing time.  - Like that will ever help.
- 蛤蜊汤怎么样？ - 什么？
- How about clam chowder?  - Again?
- 快速吃完，然后回来  - 我讨厌喝汤
- Eat fast and come back.  - I hate soup.
那就去做你的分析去吧
Then just go do your analyzing.
难道我们不能吃米饭吗？
Can't we get rice?
- 小心点，女士！ - 对不起
- Watch it, lady!  - Sorry.
- 内情简报也没用呀  - 内情简报就是个简报而已
- Damn dope sheet's not helping.  - Dope sheet's just a dope sheet.
看看它长得多好
Look how good she looks.
- 再问一下，它是多少号？ - 12号
- What's her number again?  - 12
哥们，这很那选呀
Man, this is hard.
看看它的脚步多轻盈
Watch how lightly her steps look.
- 你怎么知道？ - 今天是它的幸运日
- How can you tell?  - Today's her day.
要是我赢不了，我就惨了
If I don't win here, I'm screwed.
我警告过你第一次玩不要赌大的
I warned you not to bet big on the first game.
或许我本应在房地产试试运气的
Maybe I should've tried my luck in real estate.
好像那更容易
Like that's easy.
你在这干什么？
What are you doing here?
世界真小呀，嗯？
Small world, huh?
你怎么样？
How've you been?
我要我的钱
I want my money.
你借的那三百五十万
The $3,500 you borrowed.
- 为什么？真突然呀  - 我不是开玩笑
- Why, all of a sudden...  - I'm not kidding!
- 咱们抽支烟去  - 好
- Let's go for a smoke.  - Okay.
那么说你来这是为了找我？
So you came here looking for me?
不管怎么说，见到你很高兴，我真的很想你
Anyway, it's good to see you. I really missed you.
咱们坐下，叙叙旧吧
Let's sit down and catch up.
你的手这么冷，你吃饭了吗？
Your hand's so cold. Did you eat?
把我的钱给我就成了！
Just give me my money!
我会的，我会的
I will. I will.
- 但这么长时间…  - 嗨！
- But it's been so long...  - Hey!
就来我喜欢的样，谢谢
Just the way I like it. Thanks.
但有点苦
But it's a tad bit bitter.
那就点拿铁而不是一般的
Then just order the latte not regular.
不是一样的
It's not the same.
来一杯吗，喜秀？
Want one, Hee-su?
对了，你不喝咖啡
Right, you don't drink coffee.
你们有绿茶吗？
Do you have green tea?
有，你要来一杯吗？
Yes, would you like one?
算了吧，输了很多钱，她有点不开心
It's okay. She's a little down from losing big.
你气色不错，经常锻炼吗？
You look good. Been working out?
那边有自动取款机
There's an ATM over there.
我知道，我会给你钱的
I know. I'll pay you.
难道不奇怪吗？
Isn't it strange?
奇怪什么？
What is?
我们好久不见了，难道不应先聊聊吗？
It's been a while since we met. Shouldn't we talk first?
比方说“你怎么样？你看起来不一样”这之类的话
Like 'How've you been? ', 'You look different', and so on.
我就是来要回我的钱的，所以就快点吧
I just came to get my money back. So just hurry.
但我们刚见面，你怎么说的都是钱？
But we just met and all you talk about is money?
那很没劲
That's not fair.
没劲？
Not fair?
拿了我的钱，一年都没打个电话，你怎么还好意思这么说？
How can you say that after taking my money and not calling for a year?
都已经有一年了？
Has it been a year, already?
我想你是对的
Guess you're right.
你忘了吗？
Did you forget?
当然没有，对不起
Of course not. I'm sorry.
我来这不是接受道歉的
I didn't come for an apology.
我想的就是要回我的钱
All I want is my money back.
我还有你写给我的欠条
I still have the IOU you wrote me.
有人骗过你的钱吗？
Did someone con you out of money?
拿这个干吗？
What's with this?
我看起来像骗子吗？
Do I look like a con-man?
得了，你可以信任我
Come on, you can trust me.
好吧，我是个骗子
Fine. I'm a con-man.
我只是开个玩笑，别这样，你过去爱听我的笑话
I was just kidding. Come on. You used to laugh at my jokes.
好吧
Fine.
把你的账户写下来
Write your account number down.
你要去哪，金秀？
Where're you going Jin-su?
我有活要跑
I got an errand to run.
- 咱们喝杯咖啡吧  - 日后吧
- Let's grab a coffee.  - Later.
- 我日后把钱汇给你  - 什么？
- I'll wire it to you, later.  - What?
我会把钱打到你账上
I'll send it to your account.
不行，现在就给我
No. Just give it to me now.
我给不了，我一分钱没有
I can't. I don't have any money.
因为经济危机之类的事情
With the economic slump and all.
- 如果我知道我会遇到你，我…  - 赵秉云
- If I knew I'd bump into you I'd...  - CHO Byung-woon.
你认为我傻吗？
You think I'm stupid?
你来赌马不带钱吗？
You come to the race-track with no money?
事情不像看起来那样
It's not what it looks.
我有我的原因
I have my reasons.
想听我对你解释一切吗？
Want me to explain everything to you?
我不想听你胡说八道！
I don't want to listen to your crap!
无论如何，我今天就要我的钱
I'm getting my money today no matter what.
最后十分钟下注
10 minutes to final biddings.
这些天我相当穷
I'm pretty broke these days.
有什么不对吗，喜秀？
Is something wrong, Hee-su?
你的脸…
Your face...
或许是个新妆容吧？
Maybe it's the new make-up?
我说真的
I'm serious.
你怎么付给我钱？
How'll you pay me?
我有我的办法，今天就给你
I have my ways. I'll get it to you, today.
相信我，回家去吧
Trust me and go home.
什么？
What?
告诉过你了，不拿到钱我是不会走的
I told you I'm not leaving till I get my money.
这么说你想一直跟着我了？
So you wanna go around with me?
没错
Yes.
好吧，随你便
Employees Only Fine, whatever.
你不看比赛就走吗？
You're leaving without watching the race?
不了，突然有事
Yeah, something came up.
- 明天怎么样？ - 我尽量来
- What about tomorrow?  - I'll try to come.
明晚姑娘们要出去玩
The girls are going out tomorrow night.
真的吗？
Really?
我们打算去你说的那个酒吧
We're going to the Sake pub you told us.
要来吗？
Wanna come?
我尽量，谢谢帮我看包
I'll try. Thanks for watching my bags.
打电话给我
Call me.
太好了
So nice.
咱们走吧
Let's go.
我需要现金，你知道我的情况
I need it in cash. You know my situation.
你什么时候方便我就过去
I'll come whenever's good for you.
我先接个电话，一会打给你
I got another call. Call you right back.
你在睡觉吗？
Were you sleeping?
我给你打了好几次电话
I called you several times.
对
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
你知道
You know.
就是打个电话看看你还好吗
Just called to see how you're doing.
车不错呀，什么时候买的？
Nice car. When'd you get it?
你刚才说道哪了？
You were saying?
当然
Of course.
不是那样的
It's not that.
不，不是你想的那样
No, it's not what you think.
只是想知道，你的角膜手术怎么样了
Just wondering how your Lasik surgery went.
真的？
Really?
已经有一个月了吗？
Has it been a month, already?
时间过的真快呀
Time flies, huh?
都愈合了吗？
Then they're all healed?
我很走运眼睛没问题
I'm lucky to have good eyes.
你在哪呢？
Where are you?
釜山？
Busan?
你为什么老去那？
Why are you all the way there?
你什么时间回来？
When are you coming up?
回来后给我打电话，咱们见见面
Call me when you get back. Let's meet up.
一起吃晚饭，很好
Dinner sounds good.
好的，再见
Okay, bye.
这车看起来很新呀
The car looks fairly new.
怎么了？
Now what?
好像就是昨天我教你开车
It seems like just yesterday when I was teaching you to drive.
在阳浙江边上，记得吗？
Near Yangje River? Remember?
那么有什么计划？
So what's the plan?
都安排好了，我们只需要去拿就成了
It's all set. We just need to go get it.
- 那就告诉我去哪  - 稍等
- Then tell me where to go.  - Hold on.
对
Yeah.
什么？
What?
我电池快没电了，一会打给你
My battery's low. I'll call you right back.
把你的手机给我
Give me your phone.
这是去拿你的钱，给我
It's to get your money. Hand it over.
别这样
Come on.
就这样罢工了？
Did this just come out?
这些高科技玩意…
All this high tech...
但要是电池没电了，这东西就完全没用了
But if the battery's out, the thing's absolutely useless.
- 我们这到底是要去哪？ - 开出去
- So where The hell are we going?  - Pull out.
是我，什么时间？
It's me. What time?
我会过来的，打我这个号码
I'll come over. Call me at this number.
你这东西有电视看吗？
Do you get TV on this?
- 咱们开开电视，看看新闻吧  - 别碰它
- Let's turn it on and watch the news.  - Don't touch it.
看起来某人不缺钱呀
Doesn't look like someone hard on cash.
嗯？
Huh?
你是在问我吗？
You're asking me?
我真的很想知道，你过得怎么样？
I'm dying to know. How've you been?
你要是不说，我会胡思乱想的
I'll imagine crazy things if you don't tell me.
该死，这个真苦
Damn this is bitter.
你为什么这么生我气？
Why are you so mad at me?
什么？
What?
你觉着我生气了吗？
You think I'm angry?
你弄得好像我是你的死敌似的
You've been acting like you're with a mortal enemy.
你偷我的钱，电话不打一个，你还指望什么？
You steal my money and don't call. What'd you expect?
什么？偷？
What? Steal?
- 别这么说  - 没啥可狡辩的
- Aw, come on.  - No excuses.
- 别这样，听我把话说完  - 我不想听
- Come on, hear me out.  - I don't want to hear it.
你以前也爱吵架，但没这么厉害
You were feisty before but not this much.
你变了
You've changed.
前面街右转
Turn right up the street.
前方右转
Turn right up ahead.
这玩意真不错呀
This is pretty neat.
我应该准备好
I should get ready.
欠条
IOU
你结婚了吗？
Did you get married?
或许结了，对吧？
Probably did, right?
不关你的事
None of your business.
我们上次见面的时候
When we last met.
你辞了工作，忙着准备你的婚礼
You quit your job and were busy preparing for your wedding.
那家伙是某个大基金经理，对吧？
The guy was some big shot funds manager, right?
很奇怪呀
That's strange.
怎么了？
What is?
没什么
Oh, nothing.
呆在这，我马上回来
Stay here, I'll be right back.
等等！
Wait!
为什么我们来这？
Why are we here?
来拿你的钱，笨蛋
To get your money, silly.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
怎么了？你不相信我？
What? You don't trust me?
- 不相信  - 那和我一起来吧
- No.  - Then come with me.
嗨，你不能在那停车
Hey, you can't park there.
就停一小会，马上就走
We're just making a quick stop. We'll be right out.
访客必须把车停到地下停车场
All visitors must park in the parking lot underground.
咱们去停下车吧，喜秀
Let's just park the car, Hee-su.
我们会停停车场里的
We'll park it in the lot.
停车费每十分钟1500块
The parking fee is $1.50 for every 10 minutes.
什么？
What?
这儿？
Here?
这也是收费停车场
This is paid parking, too.
公共停车场周六是免费的
Public parking lots are free on Saturdays.
我肯定不是
Bet they're not.
- 是，是免费的  - 相信我，不免费
- No, it's free.  - Trust me, it's not.
你们要停多长时间？
How long are you staying?
- 我必须付钱吗？ - 是的，女士
- I have to pay?  - Yes, ma'am.
- 我告诉过你了  - 周六难道不是免费的吗？
- Told you.  - Isn't it free on Saturdays?
只有周日和节假日才免费
Only on Sundays and holidays.
咱们就把车停这吧
Let's just park here.
该死的
Damn it.
或许这更便宜
It's probably cheaper here.
把那东西拆来拆去，你难道不嫌烦吗？
Aren't you tired of putting that thing in and out?
你认为它会被偷吗？
Think it'll get stolen?
藏东西是我的爱好，好吗？
Hiding things is my hobby, okay?
看到没？你又生气了
See? You're mad again.
要我付停车费吗？
Want me to pay for parking?
我会付的
I'll pay.
难道你不认为是该我们坦诚地谈谈了吗？
Don't you think it's about time we start seeing things eye to eye?
对我也很难，我不知道要做什么
It's hard for me, too. I don't know what to do.
我们应该谈谈我们的未来，还有…
We should talk about our future and...
能打扰一下吗？
Excuse Me?
需要帮忙吗？
Can I help you?
我和韩总有个预约
I have an appointment with President Han?
你的名字是…
Your name is...
赵秉云
CHO Byung-woon.
她现在在楼顶上
She's on the roof at the moment.
跟我来
Follow me.
我们稍后聊
We'll talk later.
- 想等在这吗？ - 咱们走
- Wanna wait here?  - Let's go.
但外边冷
But it's cold out.
相当有劲
Pretty sharp.
打的还好吗？
Was it okay?
不错
Not bad.
但你打的有点靠下，稍微轻点
But, you're getting a little duff. Just slightly.
你说得对，为什么会这样？
You're right. Why's that?
你再握住球杆
Hold the club again.
- 再试一下  - 好的
- Try it again.  - Okay.
你的站姿和动作都很好
Your stance and posture are good.
或许是由于你触球前手腕太用力了
Maybe it's 'cuz you're using your wrists too much before impact.
我的高尔夫教练也这么说
My golf instructor said the same thing.
但我还以为我有进步了呢
But I thought I got better.
难怪我的杆数低不下来
No wonder my score isn't getting any lower.
哦，天哪！
Oh, man!
人人都有低谷期，再试试
Everyone goes through a slump. Try again.
打得好！
Nice shot!
非常完美
Just perfect.
能把手给我看看吗，女士？
May I see your hand for a sec, ma'am?
- 我的手？ - 对
- My hand?  - Yes.
看到这些老茧了吗？
See the calluses here?
这证明了你右手太用劲了
This proves you're using your right arm and hand too much.
你说得对
You're right.
想想一下，就像手里抓的是只麻雀
Think of it as holding a sparrow in your hand.
- 麻雀？真恶心  - 打个比方而已
- A sparrow? That's gross.  - So to speak.
稍等，喜秀
Hold on, Hee-su.
- 你和别人一起来的吗？ - 就是我说的那个朋友
- You came with someone?  - The friend I mentioned.
你的朋友很漂亮
Your friend is very pretty.
没这些糟糕的事前，她更漂亮
She was much prettier before things got rough.
你打高尔夫吗？
Do you golf?
不打
No.
你呢，秉云？
How about it Byung-woon?
慢节奏的运动不适合我
Slow paced sports aren't for me.
我更喜欢快节奏的运动，比方说骑马、滑雪
I'm more into fast action sports like horseback riding or skiing.
和年轻人一起玩很好
It'd be nice to play with young people.
我不喜欢和老家伙们一起玩
I hate going out on the field with old timers.
- 高尔夫是很棒的运动  - 当然是了
- Golf is a great sport.  - Of course it is.
不，谢谢
No thank you.
我最近不抽了，你也是吗？
I recently quit. You, too?
我也不抽了
I quit, too.
- 就再抽一次，嗯？ - 当然可以了
- Just one more, then?  - Sure.
- 我不喜欢一个人抽烟  - 当然了
- I don't like smoking alone.  - Of course.
那我也…
Then I'll...
哦，对了
Oh, right.
康先生？
Mr. Kang?
嗨！
Hey!
把我要的东西拿来
Bring me what I asked for.
她一直多方面帮助过我，喜秀
She's been helping me out in many ways, Hee-su.
不，正相反，是你在帮助我
No, it's the other way around. You're helping me.
但做的远远不够，夫人
But not nearly enough, ma'am.
你总是那么会说话，太可爱了
You always know just what to say. So cute.
我听说发生的事了
I heard what happened.
但我只能给你一百万
But I can only give you $1,000.
今天我有些大交易要做
I have some big transactions today.
拿着吧，谢谢她，喜秀
Take it and thank her, Hee-su.
可以吗？
Is that okay?
当然了，女士，一百万是很多的钱呀
Of course, ma'am. $1,000 is a lot of money.
我们非常感谢，对吧？
We're very thankful. Right?
听说像你这样一个年轻女人深陷这样的麻烦，我很伤心
I'm sad to hear that a young woman like you are in such trouble.
这是给你的
And this is for you.
- 这是什么？ - 是欠条
- What's this?  - It's an IOU.
欠条？
An IOU?
真有意思！你做的事都这么可爱
How sweet. Everything you do is so cute.
我本应咬破手指按血手印的
I should bite my finger and sign it in blood.
但我有点贫血
But I'm kinda anemic.
所以我就只是签了个名
So I signed it instead.
- 很好，我可不想看到你受伤  - 谢谢你
- Good. Wouldn't want you to get hurt.  - Thank you.
那么我们要走了
Then we'll be on our way.
现在就走吗？难道你们不留下来吃午饭吗？
Already? Can't you stay for lunch?
附近有家很好的鳗鱼餐厅
There's a good eel restaurant around.
鳗鱼？
Eel?
我喜欢鳗鱼，但是…
I love eel but...
下次吧，女士，我今天要帮我朋友的忙
Next time, ma'am. I gotta help out my friend, today.
给，一点小意思
Here. A sign of my appreciation.
这是给我的吗？
This is for me?
为了帮助你戒烟，我的意思是少抽点
To help you stop smoking. I mean, smoke less.
百分之九十九
99%?
有点遗憾
It's sort of sad.
是差百分之一
It's missing 1%.
正如对你而言，我也不是百分之百好
Just like I can't ever be perfect for you.
我想这就是生活
Well, that's life I guess.
你为什么走这么快？等等！
Why are you walking so fast? Wait!
怎么了？还生气吗？
What? Still angry?
至少我给你一百万了
At least you got your $1,000.
开头很不错呀
It's a great start.
高兴点，天气不错
Lighten up. It's a nice day.
我们非常感谢你的帮助？
We're very thankful for your help?
我们？我为什么要感谢她？
WE? Why do I have to be thankful to her?
感谢别人的帮助是基本礼节
It's common courtesy to thank someone for helping.
她帮的人不是我！是你！
I'm not the one she helped out! You are!
我只是来拿我的钱！
I just came to get my money!
别急，我知道
Relax. I know.
不管怎么说，那位女士可能现在心情不错
Anyway, that lady's probably in a good mood, now.
帮了我们的忙，感到高兴和自豪
Feeling happy and proud about helping us out.
给，拿着这个
Here, take this.
拿着
Come on.
从别人那借钱，但让他们觉着很高兴借给你
Borrow the money but make them feel good about lending it.
这样大家都高兴
Then everyone's happy.
你知道的，有钱人更吝啬
The rich are stingier you know.
凭空借一百万，很不容易
Lending $1000 out of the blue? That's not common.
艾米连科·菲多综合格斗大赛
M-1 Festival with Emelianenko Fedor
等等，喜秀！
Wait, Hee-su!
艾米连科菲多综合格斗大赛
M-1 Festival with Emelianenko Fedor
有好CD吗？听点音乐怎么样？
Got any good CDs? How about some music?
我在车里不听音乐
I don't listen to music in the car.
你过去随身带着满是歌曲的MP3
You used to carry around an MP3 player filled with songs.
你总让我听你最爱的歌手
You always used to make me listen to your favorite singer.
她名叫艾斯…巴特什么来着，对吧？
Her name was Ast... Bart or something, right?
艾斯特·吉芭托
Astrud Gilberto.
就是她，唱歌懒洋洋的
That's it. The drowsy singer.
但她的歌听着很舒服
Her songs were comforting, though.
- 只是好奇…  - 什么？
- Just wondering...  - What?
没什么
Nothing.
好奇什么？
What is it?
- 刚才的那个女人  - 嗯？
- That woman back there.  - Yeah?
你和她睡觉吗？
Do you sleep with her?
终于开始对我的生活感兴趣了，嗯？
Finally starting to wonder about my life, huh?
难道那不就是为什么她这么轻易给我们钱吗？
Isn't that why she gave us the money so easily?
她可能看起来简单，但她是个很杰出的女商人
She may seem naive but she's a prominent business woman.
她对钱很在乎的
She's very careful with her money.
她不会因为点爱就给别人钱的
She wouldn't give it out for being tangled in some love affair.
那她为什么要给钱？
Then why'd she do it?
或许是因为她相信我吧？
Probably 'cuz she trusts me?
你可以不信
You may laugh.
但我是个相当可靠的人，知道吗？
But I'm a pretty reliable guy, you know?
一个卷跑我的钱的可靠人？
A reliable guy who ran with my money?
嗨，我现在正在努力还你钱呢
Hey, I'm trying hard to pay you back, now.
我从她那拿到钱，因为我就是担保品
I got the money from her 'cuz I'm the collateral.
从现在起她要我做什么，我都得做
I have to do anything she asks from now on.
这么说，她要你和她睡觉，你也得干吗？
So you'll sleep with her if she wants you to?
你说的好像那是世上最糟糕的事似的
You're talking like that's the worst thing in the world.
- 你认为那很正常吗？ - 这取决于你怎么看了
- You think that's normal?  - Depends on how you look at it.
要是你觉着没啥，就没啥
If you think it's good, it's good.
要是你觉着很糟糕，那就很糟糕
If you think it's bad, then it's bad.
什么事对你来说都这么简单吗？
Everything's that simple to you?
简单点好
Simplicity is good.
我们是在给你讨债呀！
We retrieve unpaid debts for you!
这么说，你对我和她的关系感兴趣了，嗯？
So you're curious of my relationship with her, huh?
什么？
What?
想听的话，我可以多说点给你听
I can tell you more, if you want.
不用了，谢谢
No, thanks.
说实话
Be honest.
我不那么好奇，我一点都不想听
I'm so not curious. I don't need to hear any of it.
我为什么要关心你和女人那些事
Why would I care what you go around doing with women.
你一点都没变
You haven't changed one bit.
我看起来没变，是吗？
I still look the same, right?
我说三十多了，大家都不相信
People don't believe me when I say I'm over 30.
也还是这么浮躁
Still pompous, too.
别这么说
Come on.
要是我有什么变化，你会失望的
You'd be disappointed if I was any different.
喂？
Hello?
找秉云吗？
Oh, Byung-woon?
请稍等
Hold on, please.
嗨！秉云
Hey! Byung...
他不能马上接电话
He can't come to the phone right now.
请再说一遍
Pardon?
朴世美？
PARK Se-mi?
好的，再见
Okay, bye.
嗨，妈妈
Hi, mom.
我有点忙
I'm a little busy.
我不需要更多的泡菜了，我几乎从不在家吃饭
I don't need any more Kimchi. I hardly ever eat at home.
好的，妈妈
Yes, mom.
我会好好吃饭的，别担心
I'm eating well. Don't worry.
什么？
What?
好的
Okay.
我得走了，妈妈，以后打电话给你
I gotta go, mom. I'll call you later.
是你妈妈吗？
Was it your mom?
- 为什么不把电话给我？ - 为什么给你？
- Why didn't you put me on?  - Why?
这样我就能打个招呼
So I can say, hi.
- 她身体好吗？ - 很好，事怎么样了？
- How's her health?  - Good. How'd it go?
她膝盖不好，现在好点了吗？
She had a bad knee. Is it better, now?
用不着你担心
No need for you to worry.
你拿到钱了吗？
Did you get the money?
咱们再去别处看看吧，反正我也没期待太多
Let's check elsewhere. I didn't expect much, anyway.
你的众多女友不是总帮忙吗？
Your many girlfriends don't always help?
- 她是一个学校朋友，我发誓  - 随便吧
- She's a friend from school, I swear.  - Whatever.
小学同班
Same class, elementary school.
她离婚了，努力工作独自抚养女儿
She got divorced and is working hard to raise her daughter alone.
那现在你是在利用努力工作的单身母亲吗？
So now you're using hard-working single mothers?
别这么说
Aw, come on.
我本以为她情况好点了，但我想是没有
I thought things got better for her but I guess not.
全世界都在苦苦挣扎呀
The whole world's struggling.
我恨这个世界
I hate this world.
又来了，你太悲观了
There you go again being pessimistic.
- 你为什么这么…  - 认识一个叫朴世美的吗？
- Why are you so...  - Know someone named PARK Se-mi?
世美？哦，是她呀
Se-mi? Oh, her.
- 为什么问这个？ - 她打电话了
- Why?  - She called.
再把你的手机给我
Give me your phone, again.
目的地已抵达
You have arrived at your destination.
哪栋楼呀？
Which building is it?
就应该在这附近了
It should be around here.
我告诉你直走而不是右转，现在我们迷路了
I told you to go straight, not turn right. Now we're lost.
导航说右转
The navigator said to turn right.
这些玩意不总是对的，它也是人造的机器
These things aren't always right. It's just a man-made machine.
它可比某些人更可靠
It's more reliable than some people.
- 找到了  - 真的？
- Found it.  - Really?
我认为就是这栋
I think it's this one.
她肯定挣了很多钱
Man, she must've made a lot of money.
我猜经济不景气没影响到干这行的姑娘
Guess the economy doesn't affect the girls in this biz.
我就在你楼外呢
I'm just outside your building.
一路畅通
It was clear roads all the way.
真的？
Really?
好的，那慢慢洗漱吧
It's okay, wash up slowly then.
再见
Bye.
她说过一小会再来
She said to come back a little later.
等着的时候，你想做些什么？
What do you want to do while we wait?
我可没整天时间，现在快去，我在这等着
I don't have all day. Just go now, I'll wait here.
她刚醒，我得给她洗漱时间
She just woke up. I should give her time to wash-up.
又不是约会！
It's not a date!
谁在乎呀
Who cares.
咱们就等三十分钟
Let's just wait for 30 more minutes.
她上夜班，对她来说早起很困难
She works nights. It's hard for her to get up early.
当我保证你能拿到钱，好吗？
But I promise you'll get the money, okay?
你难道不饿吗？我们去吃午饭吧
Aren't you hungry? Let's go for lunch.
我们最喜欢的饭馆，难道不就在这附近吗？
Isn't our favorite restaurant around here?
叫什么名来着？
What was the name?
济州屋
Je-ju House.
没错！记得那的带鱼吗？
Right! Remember the cutlass fish?
老板很喜欢你，因为你老是会要第二份
The owner used to love you 'cuz you'd always have seconds.
我没有！
I did not!
你有
You did.
我不记得了
I don't remember.
怎么了？
What?
没什么
Nothing.
不能相信饭馆没了
I can't believe the restaurant's gone.
就是我们运气不好
Just our luck.
你认为它倒闭了吗？
Think it went out of business?
我不记得看到过很多顾客
I don't remember seeing many customers.
老板很好，也很慷慨
The owner used to be so nice and giving.
希望她还好
Hope she's doing well.
现在我们吃什么？
Now what do we eat?
咱们去吃点好吃的辣东西吧
Let's go grab something good and spicy.
从带鱼掉到了汉堡包
From cutlass fish down to hamburgers.
你知道我正餐时间是不吃汉堡的
You know I don't eat burgers at mealtimes.
我不认为那是吃饭
It's not my idea of a meal.
那就像方便面一样
It's like instant noodles.
这不是饭
This isn't a meal.
更像点心
It's more like a snack.
那就别吃
Then don't eat.
- 你要点餐吗？ - 一个香辣鸡腿堡套餐
- May I take your order?  - One Zinger Burger set, please.
- 喝什么？ - 可乐
- And your drink with that?  - Coke, please.
就这么多吗？
Will that be all?
不，我要个麦辣鸡翅汉堡套餐
No, I'll have the Spicy Burger set.
我要切成两半，把薯条换成饼干
I'd like it cut in half and a biscuit instead of fries.
还要柠檬和一些玉米沙拉
I'll have a lemonade and some corn salad, too.
- 在这吃还是带走？ - 在这吃
- For here or to go?  - Here.
总共是一万零九百块
Your total comes to $10.90, please.
我给你把切刀
I'll give you a cutting knife.
我只付我的那份
I'll just pay for my order, please.
好的
Okay...
找你的钱
Here's your change.
那个有优惠券送吗？
Do I get a coupon with that?
- 什么？ - 没什么
- What?  - Nothing.
给我尝尝，好吗？
Let me eat, will you?
想把汉堡分着吃吗？
Wanna split our burgers?
不
No.
还是不喜欢分东西给别人吃，嗯？
Still don't like sharing food, huh?
- 从我们在一起时就这样…  - 怎么了？
- Since we're together like this...  - What now?
没事
Nothing.
让我想起了过去的一些事
Brings back old memories.
很甜蜜，是吧？
It's nice, right?
该死
Damn it.
我是赵秉云
CHO Byung-woon speaking.
你在哪呢？
Where are you?
我在附近
I'm nearby.
是的
Yeah.
你能那样过来吗？
Can you go around like that?
真的吗？
Really?
对
Yes.
不是我不爱你了
It's not that I don't love you.
我只是不能再这么做了
I just can't do this anymore.
他？
Him?
他对我一直很好
He's always good to me.
谢谢理解
Thanks for understanding.
还要…
And...
对不起
I'm sorry.
嗨，好的
Hi, there.
请付1000块
$1, please.
- 稍等  - 好的
- Wait.  - Sure.
- 我还要这个  - 好的
- I'll take this, too.  - Okay.
请付1600块，谢谢
$1.60, please. Thank you.
你去哪了？我到处找你
Where'd you go? I looked everywhere.
我还以为你走了呢
I thought you left.
我为什么要走？
Why would I?
我的汉堡只吃了一半，你为什么要把它扔了？
I only ate half the burger. Why'd you throw it out?
你看起来很忙呀
You looked pretty busy.
要走了吗？
Leaving already?
再见，先生
See you around, sir.
- 再见  - 祝你好运！
- Bye.  - Good luck!
再次感谢，售票工作顺利！
Thanks again. And have fun giving out tickets!
先生？
Sir?
饶了我吧
Give me a break.
这是十万
Here's $100.
你从哪弄的？
Where'd you get this?
我当滑雪教练时，教过其中一个女孩
I taught one of the girls when I was a ski instructor.
现在向学生下手了？
Now, a student?
都长大了，爱帮助别人了，这让我很骄傲
All grown up and helping people out. Makes me proud.
- 和学生借钱吗？ - 那怎么了？
- For borrowing money from students?  - What's wrong with that?
没钱时，和别人借点，有钱时，借点给别人
When you're low, you borrow. When you're not, you give.
- 生活就是这样的  - 随你怎么说吧
- It's all a part of life.  - Whatever you say.
你借过钱给我，是不是？
You lent me money, didn't you?
你到底为什么借呢？
Why did you, anyway?
你说事很紧急，你的生意有危险
You said it was urgent. That your business was at risk!
不是因为你觉着有愧于我吗？
It wasn't 'cuz you felt sorry?
什么？
What?
那难道不是你说过的吗？
Isn't that what you said?
真不敢相信你说这话
I don't believe this.
或许是我听错了
Maybe I heard wrong.
随便吧
Anyways.
- 给  - 哇，谢谢！
- Here.  - Wow, thanks!
喝饮料或许能让你闭上嘴
Sucking on that should keep you quiet.
你还记得我喜欢罐装咖啡？
You remembered I like canned coffee?
不明白为什么人们喜欢黑咖啡和浓缩咖啡
I don't get why people drink black coffee or espressos.
罐装咖啡食用方便，味道香甜
Canned coffees are simple and sweet.
你难道不这么认为吗？
Don't you think?
喂？
Hello?
嗯
Yeah.
什么？
What?
我为什么要这样？
Why should I?
这没道理
This doesn't make any sense.
那她真是奇怪
Then she's really weird.
进来
Come in.
想来点绿茶吗？
Want some green tea?
我真的必须这么做吗？
Do I really have to do this?
她说她想先见见你
She says she wants to see you first.
这次你说了什么？
What did you say this time?
没什么，就说你在外边等着
Nothing. Just that you're waiting outside.
或许就是想打个招呼，请坐
Probably just wants to say hi. Sit down.
这个地方难道不是很棒吗？
Isn't this place, awesome?
世美
Se-mi.
- 这是喜秀，这是世美  - 这是什么？
- This is Hee-su and this is Se-mi.  - What's this?
- 给我拿点啤酒加冰  - 好的好的
- Beer in ice, For me.  - Right, Right, right.
请坐
Have a seat.
能问一下你为什么要见我吗？
May I ask why you wanted to see me?
不为什么
No reason.
- 要很多泡吗，世美？ - 是的
- Lots of foam, Se-mi?  - Yes, please.
给
Here.
- 谢谢  - 不客气
- Thank you.  - My pleasure.
我只是想看看你是谁
I just wanted to see who you were.
但我想我可能预期过高了
But I guess I had pretty high expectations.
请见谅
I beg your pardon?
你太普通了
You're so average.
我本以为你很特殊
I imagined you'd be something special.
超级漂亮
Stunningly beautiful.
至少也是很优雅美丽
Or overly elegant and classy.
因为秉云说，你们俩曾那么亲密
Since Byung-woon said you two were close that is.
别开玩笑了，世美
Stop kidding around, Se-mi.
我是说真的，那样才配得上你
I'm serious. You deserve that much.
她完全配不上你
You're way over her league.
她喜欢开玩笑
She loves to kid around.
你过去非常喜欢他，是吧？
You used to like him a lot, right?
难道那不就是你借钱给他的原因吗？
Isn't that why you lent him the money?
如果是那样的话，你为什么还要向他追债？
If you did, why are you hounding him?
要是我是你，我会直接把钱送给他
If I were you, I would've just given it to him.
世美，别说了
Se-mi, please.
你屁都不知道！怎么这么放肆！
You don't know anything! How dare you!
- 喜秀，坐下…  - 闭嘴！什么破事！
- Hee-su, let's sit down and...  - Shut up! What is this!
我为什么必须听她这么说？
Why do I have to listen to that?
都是因为你！
It's all because of you!
你都等了一年了，难道就不能再稍微多等会吗？
If you waited for a year, couldn't you wait a little longer?
想过这么突然和他要钱，他有多难吗？
Ever think how hard it's on him asking for money out of the blue?
你一定要这么折腾他吗？
Must you put him through that shit?
什么？
What?
那他折腾我呢？
What about the shit he put me in?
世美！喜秀目前有困难
Se-mi! Hee-su has it rough these days.
秉云！别和个天使似的！
Byung-woon! Stop acting like an angel!
为点破钱吵架，真没劲
Bickering over a few lousy bucks. So lame.
对你这种赚快钱的女人而言
For girls like you who make easy money...
三百五十万可能不多，但对我可不一样！
$3500 may not be much. But it is for me!
别装优雅了！你不就是个酒吧女吗！
Stop acting classy! You're nothing but a bargirl!
哦！哎呀！
Oh! Geeze!
你们俩扯太远了
You're both taking it too far.
我想你说得对
Guess you're right.
我不是什么你说的优雅的人
I'm not what you'd call classy.
非常对不起，二位
I'm so sorry to both of you.
都是因为我，非常对不起
This is all 'cuz of me. I'm so sorry.
骂我吧，姑娘们，好吗？
Just yell at me, girls. Please?
是我的错，我应该跪求原谅
It's my fault. I'll kneel for forgiveness.
- 喜秀，对不起  - 咱们走！
- Hee-su, I'm sorry.  - Let go!
对不起
Sorry.
世美，请你…
Se-mi, please...
你这是在干什么？
What are you doing?
起来
Get up.
对不起，夫人
I'm sorry, lady.
我肯定是脑子出问题了
I must've lost it or something.
我有点故意态度不好
I was kinda rude on purpose.
我是有点无礼，大家都知道
I'm known to be a little saucy.
看到没？我知道她是在开玩笑
See? I knew she was kidding.
这才是我认识的世美
Now that's the Se-mi, I know.
- 这是恭维吗？ - 当然了
- Is that a compliment?  - Of course.
随你怎么说吧
Whatever you say.
你好？
Hello?
- 要喝绿茶吗，喜秀？ - 他是谁？
- Want some green tea, Hee-su?  - Who's this?
嗨，亲爱的
Hi, honey.
就在家当乖女孩呢
Just being a good girl at home.
我这有人
I have someone over.
好的，我会打电话给你
Okay, I'll call you.
忘了我刚才说的话吧
Ah, forget what I said earlier and...
嗨，女士
Hey, lady.
别在意
Don't sweat it.
这是七十万
Here's $700.
- 哥哥，你不用打扫  - 小会就好
- You don't have to clean that up.  - It'll just take a sec.
现在的姑娘都像模特
Girls these days are like models.
一定是注意饮食了
Must be somethin' in the food.
有什么不对吗？
What's wrong?
奇怪我和世美的关系，是吗？
Wondering about my relationship with Se-mi, are you?
别伤心
Don't get upset.
我一直受女士欢迎
I was always popular with the ladies.
- 但不是你想的那样  - 不是那样
- But it's not what you think.  - It's not that.
那是哪样？
Then what is it?
我明白了
I get it.
什么？
What?
看起来你没怎么变
Looks like you haven't changed much.
你刀子嘴豆腐心
You act tough but you're a softy in heart.
你可不了解我
You don't know me.
别担心，她不会被你的话伤着的
Don't worry. She didn't get hurt by what you said.
你怎么知道她的感受？
How do you know how she feels?
她经历过很多，她是个坚强的女孩
She's been through a lot in life. She's a tough girl.
那不表示她的感情从不会被伤害
That doesn't mean her feelings will never get hurt.
我的意思只是她已经习惯了
I just meant she's used to it.
你怎么能这么说？
How can you say that?
我说什么了？
What did I say?
你是谁，你怎么知道她是受到了伤害没有？
Who are you to judge whether her feelings were hurt or not?
这没什么可吵的
It's nothing to argue about.
你可曾伤过心吗？
Have you ever had your feelings hurt?
你知道那是什么感觉吗？
Do you know what it's like?
你的鞋带开了，肯定有人想你了
Your laces are undone. Someone must be thinking of you.
- 别弄了  - 别动
- Leave it.  - Hold still.
你是对的，我从未那么伤心过
You're right. I've never been that hurt.
但或许有一点点伤心
But maybe just a little.
就在你说你想分手之后
After you said you wanted to break up.
我永远忘不了你脸上的表情
I could never forget the look on your face.
那表情很奇怪
It was strange.
我以前从未见过
I haven't seen it before.
但你看起来…
But you looked...
真的很高兴
Really happy.
我认为你和我在一起很高兴
I thought you were happy with me
但我们分手时你看起来更高兴
but you looked happier when we broke up.
那种感觉闪了一下
I'd get flashes of that.
感到有点伤心
And felt kinda hurt.
你好
Hello?
嗨
Oh, hi.
就是去办点事
Just going around on business.
是的
Yes.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
非常感谢
Thanks a lot.
你是最棒的，谢谢了
You're the best. Thanks.
秉…云吗？
Byung-woon?
咦？
Huh?
我一会给你回电话
I'll call you right back.
嗨
Hey.
- 你在这干什么？ - 顺便路过
- What are you doing here?  - Just stopping by.
你住在这吗？
Do you live here?
我公婆住这
My in-laws live here.
哦
Oh.
你来参加过我们的婚礼，对吧？
You came to our wedding, right?
- 你记得我吗？ - 当然了
- You remember Me?  - Of course.
我们在迎宾处打赌，看谁喝米酒最多
We bet who could drink the most rice wine at the reception.
你就记得这个呀
That's some memory you got there.
他在厕所吐了一宿，差点死了
He almost died throwing up at the toilet all night long.
- 你们还要去别的地方吗？ - 是的
- Are you on your way somewhere?  - Yes.
咱们为什么不喝一杯呢？
Why don't we grab a quick drink?
对不起，我们得去和别人碰面
Sorry, but we have to meet someone.
十分钟就成了，这的咖啡很不错
Just 10 minutes, then. The cafe here is nice.
是呀，就一小会
Yeah, just for a while.
下次吧，红珠
Maybe next time, Hong-ju.
你要喝点什么？
What would you like to drink?
我喝咖啡，速溶的，多加糖和奶
I'll have coffee, instant style, with lots of sugar and milk, please.
好的
Okay.
你来绿茶吗？
Green tea for you?
好的，我要绿茶
Yes, I'll have green tea.
咱们喝啤酒吧，今天是周六，来扎啤
Let's drink beer. It's Saturday. Draft beers, please.
您点的马上就来
I'll be right back with your order.
嗯，爸爸？
Yes, pops?
是
Yeah.
你近来怎么样？
How've you been?
我听说不太好呀
I heard things weren't good.
怎么能老是好呢
Well, it can't always be good.
真的吗？我碰上了红珠的一些朋友
Really? I met some of Hong-ju's friends.
我真喜欢你的打扮
I really like your style.
我们点了啤酒
We ordered beer.
简约而又知性
Moderate and intellectual.
得了，爸爸
Aw come on, pops.
知道吗？他在学校很出名
You know? He was famous in school for
因为对女人很有品味
having high standards in women.
这是恭维，是吧？
It's a compliment, right?
当然了
Of course.
来了
Here it comes.
给
Here.
谢谢
Thank you.
碰杯
Shall we?
你经营一家木材公司，是吧？
You ran a lumber company, right?
不干了，现在我在找人投资新商业计划
Not anymore. I'm now looking for investors to a new business plan.
嗯
Okay...
- 服务员  - 你好
- Waitress?  - Yes?
再来一杯啤酒
Another beer, please.
什么生意？
What business?
关于国际餐饮业的
Sort of an international restaurant business.
你过去和我老婆约会过，是吧？
You used to date my wife, right?
大熙，别说了
Dae-hee, please.
有一次她喝的酩酊大醉，不停地念叨你
Once when she got really drunk, she rambled on about you.
她可能记不得了
Probably doesn't even remember.
所以我想见见你，问问你
So I wanted to meet you and ask you.
大学的时候
We were just in
我们只是在同一个马术俱乐部而已
horseback riding club together in college.
- 对吧，红珠？ - 没错
- Right, Hong-ju?  - Right.
- 我初学，而你是资深会员  - 对
- I was a freshman and you're a senior.  - Right.
但你说过他是你的初恋
But you said he was your first love.
嗯，大学的时候…你也知道…
Well, back in college... You know...
我们是那种非常亲近的朋友
We were sort of close friends.
是的
Right.
亲近到睡到一起吗？
Close enough to sleep together?
只是问问而已吗
Just asking.
谢谢
Thank you.
你难道不去追她吗？
Shouldn't you go after her?
她会马上回来的
She'll be right back.
- 干杯  - 好的
- Drink up.  - Sure.
她来了
Here she comes.
我应该点些吃的吗？
Should I order some food?
有什么你想吃的吗？
Anything you want to eat?
点点东西，喜秀
Pick something, Hee-su.
对不起
I'm sorry.
再这么做，我会杀了你
Do that again and I'll kill you.
好的，喝酒
Okay. Have a drink.
谢谢
Thank you.
喝的头疼
Damn hangover.
你为什么喝那么多？
Why'd you drink so much?
我能怎么说，说不吗？
How can I say, no?
至少我们弄到了三十万
At least we got $300.
和陌生人借钱，你真有本事
Borrowing money from strangers. You're something.
大家说我都能把空调卖到北极去
People say I could probably sell air conditioners in the North Pole.
生存高手，但是个骗子，骗人的餐饮业…
A survivor but a liar. Phony restaurant business...
- 我可没说谎，想听听吗？ - 不想
- I wasn't lying. Wanna hear it?  - No.
你的电话响了
Your phone's ringing.
或许又是我的
It's probably for me, again.
你好？
Hello?
- 你后座的包  - 嗯？
- Your bag in The back.  - Yeah?
你为什么随身带着这么大的东西？
Why do you carry around such a big thing?
我一直住在一个朋友那
I was staying at a friend's place.
他兄弟从部队回来了，所以我就搬出来了
His brother got back from the army so I moved out.
- 这么说你无家可归？ - 对
- So you're homeless?  - Yup.
我有点缺钱，所以我卖了房子
I was a little short on cash, so I sold my place.
你仍旧玩赛马
And you still hang around race-tracks.
不是赌钱，过去赌过，但现在不了
It's not to make money. I used to, but it's not that anymore.
那你为什么去那？
Then why do you go there?
记得我梦想成为骑手吗？
Remember my dream of becoming a jockey?
要不是我这么大个，没准我就成了呢
If I didn't get so big, I probably would've made it.
我被迫放弃了梦想，但我仍旧喜欢去那
I had to give up my dream but I still love being there.
看着骑手骑着马
Watching the jockeys riding the horses
让我心情激动
makes my heart jump.
你为什么停车？
Why are you stopping?
咱们算了吧
Let's drop it.
你什么意思？
What do you mean?
咱们就这分开吧
Let's just split up here.
你疯了吗？这次又是那出？
Are you mad again? What is it this time?
事情不是那样的
It's not that.
我没法再干了
I can't do this.
那钱怎么办？
Then what about the money?
- 我们都快到了  - 就电汇给我吧
- We're almost there.  - Just wire it into my account.
既然开始了就去拿钱吧
Take the money while we're on it.
我想今天全部还你
I want to give it all to you today.
先这样吧，算了吧
Forget it. Just drop it.
你来真的是为钱吗？
Did you really come For The money?
你什么意思？
What do you mean?
很奇怪，你那么想要你的钱
It's strange how you wanted your money
现在又突然不了
and now you suddenly don't.
肯定有别的原因
There's gotta be another reason.
什么原因？
Like what?
比方说你想念我？
Like you missed me?
你饶了我吧
Give me a break.
在前边的路口左转
Turn left at the intersection ahead.
听到了吗？咱们走吧
Hear that? Let's go.
我说过，不！
I said, no!
西班牙人和韩国人有许多共同点
Spaniards and Koreans have many things in common.
例如整晚开派对，饮酒
Like partying all night, drinking.
脾气有点急躁
And being a little quick tempered.
还有…
And...
加点满天星怎么样？
How about adding some baby's breath to that?
马蹄莲配鸢尾花更好
Callas go better with irises.
多加一万块，我可以加些鸢尾花
I can mix in some irises for $10 more.
- 不用了，就这样吧  - 好的
- No, that's fine.  - Okay.
马蹄莲本身就很好看
The callas look beautiful as they are.
西班牙人口味也类似
Spaniards also have similar tastes.
他们和我们一样，喜欢咸辣食物，吃米饭
They like spicy and salty foods and eat rice like us.
他们的什锦饭有点像我们的泡菜炒饭
Their Paella is kinda like our Kimchi fried rice.
所以我认为米酒在西班牙也会畅销
So I think rice wine will do well in Spain.
在马德里的中心开家米酒俱乐部
A rice wine pub in the heart of Madrid.
听起来很棒，对吧？
Sounds sweet, huh?
招牌上写“高档米酒，来自韩国”
The sign will say, 'High Quality Rice Wine from Korea.'
我顺便也卖泡菜和泡菜饼
And I'll sell Kimchi and Korean pancakes to go along.
成，随你便
Sure. Whatever.
这难道不是很棒吗？想一起做生意吗？
Isn't it great? Wanna go in business together?
不，我没你有梦想
No. I'm no dreamer like you.
在西班牙开家米酒俱乐部，主意真棒
A rice wine pub in Spain. Great idea.
难道不是吗？
Isn't it?
看到没？大家都认为那是个好主意
See? Everyone thinks it's a great idea.
这是肯定的，我可以告诉你
It's a sure thing, I tell 'ya.
闻闻这个，喜秀
Smell this, Hee-su.
不
No.
很好闻
It's good.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢，喜秀
Thanks, Hee-su.
- 你什么时候去过西班牙？ - 我很快就会去的
- When did you visit Spain?  - I'll go someday soon.
哇！酷！
Wow! Cool!
我们必须得总像这样碰面吗？
Must we always meet, like this?
你为什么去杨平？
Why were you in Yang-pyung?
买点猪排
To buy some pork chops.
对，杨平的牛排是最棒的！
Right, Yang-pyung pork chops are the best!
- 好久不见了  - 嗨
- Long time no see.  - Hi.
把这个替我给你夫人
Give this to your wife, for me.
- 和我来取钱吧  - 好的
- Come with me to get the money.  - Oh, okay.
上来吧
Come on up.
你也来吧，喜秀
You too, Hee-su.
这难道不是很棒吗？
Isn't this nice?
- 多少钱？ - 很贵
- How much was it?  - Pretty expensive.
- 我们马上就出来，好吗？ - 当然了
- We're coming right out, right?  - Of course.
- 稍微吃点之后  - 这不是野餐
- After a quick bite.  - This isn't a picnic.
如果你有啤酒和猪排，这就是野餐
It's a picnic if you got beer and pork chops.
刚才我只吃了半个汉堡
I only had half the hamburger before.
就吃一块猪排，我们就马上出来
Just one pork chop and we'll be right out.
小心楼梯
Watch the stairs.
- 你吃饱了吗？ - 嗨，那边
- Did you get enough to eat?  - Hi, there.
小心楼梯
Watch the stairs.
你骑着摩托车看起来很棒，哥们
The bike looks good on you, man.
我想卖了这个旧地方，但我老婆喜欢这
I wanna sell this old place but the wife likes it.
太棒了！风景真好
It's great! You have an awesome view.
进来吧
Come on in.
你什么时候建的这？酷！
When did you build this? Cool!
花了整一个星期
This took a whole week.
亲爱的，醒醒
Hon? Wake up.
我也来了
I'm here, too.
嗨，秉云
Hi, Byung-woon.
生日快乐！
Happy birthday!
谢谢
Thank you.
你为什么喝这么多？
Why'd you drink so much?
姑娘们把我灌的
The girls put me up to it.
我没办法
I had no choice.
进来，喜秀
Come in, Hee-su.
- 不了，我就在这等着吧  - 进来吧
- No, I'll just wait here.  - Come on in.
你还要举办展览吗？
Are you holding another exhibition?
- 下个月  - 真的？
- Next month.  - Really?
你们曾经在一起，是吧？
You came together once, right?
- 是的  - 没错
- Yes.  - That's right.
- 你好  - 嗨
- Hello.  - Hi.
- 这还真干净呀  - 啤酒是热的，亲爱的
- Lots of neat stuff Here.  - The beer's hot, hon.
给我来个凉的
Get me a cold one.
好的
Okay.
这的啤酒都没了
The beer's all gone here.
- 秉云  - 嗯
- Byung-woon?  - Yeah?
- 出去烧烤吧  - 好的
- Go out and barbecue.  - Sure.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
谢谢，但不是什么大事
Thanks, but it's no big deal.
你是水瓶座的吗？
Are you an Aquarius?
是的
Yes.
那你们俩不太合适
Then you two aren't a good match.
我们不是在约会
We're not dating.
水瓶座很容易在危难时离开别人
Aquarius tend to leave people easily in bad situations.
- 啤酒要吗？ - 谢谢
- Beer?  - Thank you.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
没事，一看到你表哥，我就有这样的感觉
Nothing. I get like this whenever I see your cousin.
别说了
Don't get started.
为什么他活得那样？
Why does he live like that?
你为什么一个人在这？
Why are you here alone?
我不喜欢人多
I don't like a big crowd.
我也是
Me, neither.
你不想和我聊聊吗？
You don't want to talk to me?
嗯？
Huh?
但我可很想和你聊天
But I've been dying to talk to you.
请坐
Have a seat.
爱喜，抽吗？
Menthols, okay?
表兄弟？
Cousins?
他是你表弟吗？
Is he your younger cousin?
不，我们同岁
No, we're the same age.
我的生日还更大点
My birthday's a little faster.
那为什么你看起来那么老？
Then why do you look so old?
你还说别人
You should talk.
你看起来都50多了
You look way past 50.
那是因为我过过苦日子
It's 'cuz I had a tough life.
但他像个王子一样长大
But he grew up like a prince.
- 他不显老是因为他幼稚  - 是的，我是有点不成熟
- He never gets old 'cuz he's childish.  - That's right. I'm a little immature.
女人喜欢那样的男人
Women like that in men.
我忙的屁股不着地，他继承了家族生意
I'd work my butt off and he'd inherit the family business.
然后他把家里所有钱都弄没了
Then he went and lost all the money in the family.
甚至他老婆都抛弃了他
Even his wife ran out on him.
真的吗？她跑了？
Really? She ran away?
- 闭嘴，那是隐私  - 哥们，真糟糕
- Shut up. That's private.  - Man, that sucks.
我意识到男人需要金钱和权力
I realized a man needs to have money and power.
当然，男人需要
Of course, he does.
你真不成熟，你们俩都是
You're so immature. Both of you.
我只是说我担心他
Just saying I'm worried about him.
我帮过他多少次了？
How many times did I help him out?
那下次就袖手旁观吧
Just watch it next time.
这么说我是坏人了？
So I'm the bad guy, huh?
算了吧
Forget it.
没事，大家都知道
It's okay. Everyone knows.
谁还要猪排？
More pork chops anyone?
- 请来块熟的  - 没问题
- A well done one, please.  - Sure thing.
- 给我拿个香肠  - 好的
- And get me a sausage.  - Okay.
在感恩节上我看见他父亲了，他情况很不好
I saw his dad at Thanksgiving. He was a mess.
我希望他不会太担心他父亲
I wish he wouldn't worry his dad so much.
但有时候我也嫉妒他
But there are times, when I envy him.
无论事情多糟糕，他好像都不烦心
No matter how hard things get, it doesn't seem to bother him.
他有个疯狂的想法，要在西班牙开个俱乐部什么的
He's got a crazy idea of opening up a pub in Spain or something.
- 西班牙？ - 对
- Spain?  - Yes.
难道他没告诉你吗？
Didn't he tell you about that?
饱了
That's enough.
- 给你个新烤的  - 咱们走吧
- Here's a fresh round.  - Let's go.
什么？我们还没吃呢
What? We didn't even eat yet.
我的香肠在哪？
Where's my sausage?
- 哦，好的  - 咱们走吧！
- Oh, right.  - Let's just go!
等等
Wait.
给你香肠
Here's your sausage.
- 谢谢  - 马上回来
- Thanks.  - Be right back.
你不高兴吗？
Are you upset?
我表弟就那样
My cousin's like that.
大家开始都误解他
People mistake him at first.
但他从内心讲是个好人
But he's a good guy at heart.
在他那样对你后，你怎么还能这么说？
How can you say that after what he did to you?
他对我怎么了？
What did he do?
难道你听到一点赞扬之词了吗？难道你不生气吗？
Don't you have any pride? Aren't you angry?
你说得对
You're right.
现在我想想这事
Now that I think about it.
他太让我生气了！
Ooo he makes me mad!
跑了的老婆是怎么回事？
What's with the runaway wife?
那个呀，我离婚了
Oh, that. I got divorced.
实际上，她踹了我
Actually, she divorced me.
你一年内既结婚又离婚？
You got married and divorced all in one year?
没啥好说的
What can I say.
生意垮了的时候，她把事看的很严重
When the business went down, she took it real hard.
于是我就让她走了
So I let her go.
我不想看到她因为我而不幸福
I didn't want to see her unhappy 'cuz of me.
我想我可能是个不错的人
I guess I could be a pretty nice guy.
这种事你怎么都能开玩笑呢？
How can you joke about something like that?
过去的就过去了
Well, what's past is past.
我永远都搞不清你是不是认真的
I can never tell if you're being sincere or not.
我知道我有点简单
I know I can be a little simple.
但我一直是认真的
But I've always been sincere.
好了，算了吧
Okay. Drop it.
为什么我认真的时候你总是打断我？
Why do you always cut me off when I'm being serious?
别认真了，嘻嘻哈哈最适合你
Don't get serious. Joking around suits you best.
明白
Gotcha.
咱们就去弄钱吧
Let's just go get the money.
只差九十万了
We have only $900 left to go.
那我现在我可以直接进去了吗？
So I can come right in, now?
教师办公室吗？谢谢
The teachers' room? Thank you.
是在一楼吗？
Is it on the first floor?
我们能从这过去吗？
Can we go thru here?
谢谢，祝你愉快
Thank you. Have a nice day.
咱们走，喜秀
Let's go, Hee-su.
我能把车停这吗？
Can I park the car here?
当然可以，那辆车就停在这
Sure. That car's parked here.
你不把导航藏起来吗？
You're not hiding the navigator?
算了吧
Forget it.
你确定吗？
You sure?
怎么了？
What?
好现象
It's a good thing.
我很高兴你没变
I'm glad you didn't change.
你在说什么呢？
What are you talking about?
我知道你总是会进步的，或早或晚
I knew you'd always be doing well somewhere.
我喜欢你这点
I liked that about you.
别装正经了，我告诉过你那不适合你
Don't act serious. I told you, it doesn't suit you.
你总是知道你在干什么
You always knew what you were doing.
很好，除了有点倔强
Perfect. Except for that feisty side.
我就喜欢你这样
I like you the way you are.
- 永不改变  - 什么？别说了
- Don't ever change.  - What? Stop it.
- 想跑跑暖和一下吗？ - 不
- Wanna run to keep warm?  - No.
我也不想
Me neither.
- 你是找素妍的吧？ - 对
- Are you here for So-yeon?  - Yes.
- 嗨，我是她老师  - 你好
- Hi, I'm her teacher.  - Hello.
你是她叔叔吗？
You're her uncle?
准确地说不是，但也差不多
Well not exactly, but sort of.
你要打电话确认一下吗？
Would you like to call and check?
不用了，没事
No, it's okay.
你来早了…
You're early...
那边下去，到隔壁楼
Go down that way to the next building.
她在一楼，你可以带她回家
She's on the first floor. You can take her home.
谢谢
Thank you.
她父母很信任你，这种事都让你帮忙吗？
Her parents trust you enough to ask for favors like this?
她从小就很喜欢我
She liked me a lot ever since she was little.
我很受小孩欢迎
I'm pretty popular with the kids.
我猜你很合适和小孩在一起
Bet you fit right in with them.
不是，那是因为我理解他们看世界的角度
No, it's 'cuz I can relate to how they look at the world.
是这样吗？
Is that so?
素妍在有些方面很像你
So-yeon's a lot like you in some ways.
她聪明但很有个性
She's smart but has one heck of a personality.
但我从未被停学
But I never got suspended from school.
人人都有缺点
Everyone suffers from something.
素妍、我和你，我们都是
So-yeon, me, you... We all do.
甚至是那边的学校门卫
Even the school guard back there.
回到学校的感觉真奇怪
It feels weird being back at school.
激起了许多感受，你呢？
Brings back a lot of emotions. How about you?
这些孩子们在哪呢？
Where are all the kids?
或许老师告诉我们错了地方
Maybe the teacher told us the wrong place.
她在哪呢？
Where is she?
- 我没结婚  - 嗯？
- I didn't get married.  - Huh?
没什么
Nothing.
喂，等一下！
Hey, wait!
你认识一个叫严素妍的学生吗？
Do you know a student named EUM So-yeon?
不知道
Sorry.
好的，好好干吧
Okay, keep up the good work.
我要去再问问老师
I'll go ask the teacher again.
你在干什么呢？
What are you doing?
你说什么？
Pardon?
你在干什么呢？
What are you doing?
铲口香糖
Scraping off gum.
为什么干这个？
What's this for?
填满那个，我就可以回家了
If I fill that up, I can go home.
那不是我的错
It's not my fault.
我不能整天盯着她
I can't go around keeping an eye on her all day.
学生也有他们的权利
Students have their rights.
她的手机关机了
Her cell phone's off.
我们难道不应该报她失踪吗？
Shouldn't we report her missing?
她只不见了一个小时
She's only been gone for an hour.
严女士吗？
Mrs. EUM?
你最后和素妍通话是在什么时候？
When did you last speak with So-yeon?
见到你最喜欢的秉云叔叔，难道你不高兴吗？
Aren't you glad to see your favorite Uncle B?
我很想念你，伙计
I missed you big time, kiddo.
我们有一年没见了吧？
Has it been a year, since we met?
别激动
Relax.
有两年了
It's been two years.
没错
Oh, that's right.
我可以自己回家，秉云叔叔，放心吧
I can go home by myself, Uncle B. Just go.
你难道不是在约会吗？
Aren't you on a date?
那是我们三个人的约会！
A date for all three of us, then!
你担心我会再跑掉吗？
You're worried that I'll run off again?
得了，我们是朋友，我从不那么想
Come on, we're pals. I'd never think that.
你不必这么说
You don't have to say that.
你喜欢什么样的音乐？你在听什么？
What kind of music do you like? What were you listening to?
好像我告诉你，你就知道似的
Like you'd know if I told you.
我当然知道，你知道阿瑟…金…金布瑞克吗？
Of course I would. Do you know Astru... Gil... Gilbrake?
怎么了？
What?
车被拖走了
It got towed.
你说我可以把车停这！
You said I could park here!
他们周六也拖车吗？
They have towing on Saturdays?
真是工作努力呀！
Some diligent workers...
我的包…包在车上
My bag... it's in the car.
哦，不
Oh, no.
我们去把车取回来，离这不远
We'll go get the car back. It's not far from here.
来吧
Come on.
放开！
Let go!
要手帕吗？
Want a handkerchief?
素妍呢？好的
So-yeon? Good.
嗨，这是残疾人专座
Hey, this is the handicapped seat.
坐这或许也成
It's probably okay to sit there.
你不想见到我，对吗？
You don't wanna see me, right?
想要我做到别的地方吗？
Want me to sit somewhere else?
好吧，我去别的地方
Fine. I'll go somewhere else.
我走
I'm going.
对不起，我觉着好像都是我的错
I'm sorry. I feel like it's my fault.
不是，当然不是
No, of course it's not.
都是我的错
It's all my fault.
那是为什么？
Why's that?
遇人不淑
For meeting the wrong person.
我猜他可能很孩子气
I guess he can be pretty childish.
但我仍旧觉着秉云叔叔不错，他不那么坏
But I still think Uncle B is okay. He's not that bad.
你为什么逃学？
Why did you skip school?
对不起，我不应该问的
Sorry. I shouldn't have asked.
就是喜欢逃学
Just felt like it.
为什么我们不打个车呢？
Why don't we catch a cab?
地铁更快
The subway's faster.
- 靠近点，你会淋湿的  - 不用，谢了
- Get closer. You're getting wet.  - No, Thank you.
- 看到没？都湿了  - 我没事
- See? It's all wet.  - I'm fine.
咱们坐下一趟吧，喜秀
Let's take the next one, Hee-su.
等等！
Wait up!
屏蔽门即将关闭
The screen doors are closing.
我告诉过你我们应该坐下一趟
I told you we should catch the next one.
怎么了？你受伤了吗？
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
我想我扭脚脖子了
I think I sprained my ankle.
但会没事的
But it'll be okay.
我只是想…
I just wanted to...
快点去取车
go get the car faster.
哥们，你真是很快呀
Man, you're pretty fast.
坐下吧
Sit down.
不用，我没事
No, I'm okay.
艾米连科·菲多综合格斗大赛
M-1 Festival with Emelianenko Fedor
六十亿分之一世界最强男即将到来
One in 6 billion, the strongest man in the world coming your way.
菲多
Fedor.
我过去从不喜欢格斗运动
I never used to like combat sports.
但有一天我在电视上偶然看到他
But I saw him by chance on TV one day.
他看起来就像邻居家普通友好的哥们
He looked like the average, nice guy next door.
在台上等待时他很腼腆
He looked so shy waiting up on the ring.
但当比赛开始时，这家伙就完全变了
But when the game started, the guy completely changed.
他就开始猛击对手
He started pounding away at his opponent.
我从未见过像他这样的人
I've never seen anything like him.
他和我见过的选手都不一样
He's nothing like any fighter I've ever seen.
场内不可战胜，场外乐意助人，就像超人一样
Invincible on the ring, but a kind helper outside like a superhero.
有一次我躺下
Once when I was down.
我在梦里看到了他，他甚至说韩语
I saw him in my dream. He even spoke Korean.
他说“你还好吗？感觉怎么样？”
He said, 'Are you okay? How are you feeling? '
我感到非常快乐，说“我现在好了，谢谢你”
I felt overcome with joy and said, 'I'm okay now, thanks to you.'
很神奇，但有一段时间我的确感到好多了…
It's amazing, but for a while I actually felt better and...
怎么了？
What's wrong?
该死…
Oh, darn...
这有很多人和我们一样
There's a lot of people here like us.
至少我们不孤单，高兴点，喜秀
At least we're not alone. Cheer up, Hee-su.
真是糟糕！
What the!
这是怎么了？
What's wrong with this?
- 让我来试试  - 别碰它
- Let me try.  - Don't touch it.
- 你会弄断的  - 不会，别担心
- You'll just break it.  - No, don't worry.
这可能有用
This might help.
你为什么没结婚？
Why didn't you get married?
我做不到
I couldn't do it.
基本上是我离开了他
Basically, I left him.
他的一个员工盗用了一些钱
One of his workers embezzled some cash
他也失业了
and he lost his job, too.
就在婚礼前突然没了工作…
Suddenly out-of-work right before the wedding...
他建议我们分手
He suggested we break up.
所以我就分了，正如我期待的那样
So I did. Like I've been waiting for it.
我很坏，是不是？
Bad, aren't I?
更糟糕的是再找个工作不是很容易
To make matters worse, it wasn't easy to find another job.
我不能再从基层干起了
I couldn't start at the bottom, again.
这东西怎么会变成这样呢？
How in the world did this get like this?
你难道就不能认真一次吗？
Can't you be serious for once!
我听着呢
I was listening.
算了，上车吧
Forget it. Get in.
你有胶带吗？
Do you have any duct tape?
赶快上车！
Just get in!
听起来有点像我的故事
Sounds kinda like my story.
什么？
What?
你知道的，他和我
You know. Him and me.
当情况不好时，让他的女人离开
Sending his woman away when things turned bad.
使我想起了某个电影明星，他曾说过…
Reminds me of some movie star who once said...
“我们分手因为我们真心相爱”
'We're breaking up because we truly love each other.'
那在西班牙开俱乐部的主意怎么样呢？
So how about the pub in Spain idea?
我说过不咋样
I said, no.
来点吗？
Want some?
味道不错，甜甜的吧？
Nice and sweet, huh?
别这样
Stop it.
你说过你喜欢我的这边脸
You said you liked this side of my face.
所以我总习惯站在你左边
So I always used to stand on your left.
- 我想告诉你  - 什么？
- I wanted to yell at you.  - What?
如果你那时说你没钱
If you said you didn't have the money,
我本打算嚷嚷一下就走的
I was just going to yell and go.
我听够了嚷嚷了，也不都是你
I've had enough yelling. Not you, too.
- 但是那很好  - 什么很好？
- Still, it was nice.  - What was?
因为你来找我了
'Cuz you came looking for me.
随你怎么说吧
Yeah, whatever.
看到没？我们今天做的很好
See? We did good, today.
离三百五十万非常近了
We're pretty close to $3500.
一整天都借钱还我很好吗？
Borrowing money all day to pay me was good?
但因为我们一起做，所以我们能做到
But we could do it 'cuz we're together.
要是一个人干就很辛苦了
It would've been hard doing it alone.
再打一下电话，要是还得晚点，我就走了
Call again. I'll just go, if it's any later.
给我钥匙，我把手机落里边了
Give me the keys. I left the phone inside.
你拿着这个
You can have this.
你和秉云一起来的，对吗？
You came with Byung-woon, right?
是的
Yes.
你怎么…
How did you...
早些时候我在商店前见过你
I saw you in front of the store, earlier.
我记得你
I remember you.
哦，是了
Oh, right.
让你来两次很抱歉
Sorry to make you come twice.
- 秉云去哪了？ - 就是去车里取点东西了
- Where's Byung-woon?  - Just getting something from the car.
- 妈妈，美少女战士  - 等一下，宝贝
- Mommy, 'Sailor Moon'.  - Hold on, sweetie.
我给你钥匙，和她说再见，自己回家去
I'll give you the keys. Say goodnight to her and go on in.
晚安
Goodnight.
哦！
Oh!
这是四十万
Here's $400.
我没有信封装
I didn't have an envelope.
让你等了一整天很不好意思
Sorry to keep you waiting all day.
我听说他欠了你一年了
I heard he didn't pay you back for a year.
你也知道他对钱比较不在意
You know he's loose with money.
但是…
But...
我…
I...
我不能收这钱
I can't take this.
你来难道不是为了这个吗？
Didn't you come for this?
是，但是…
Yes, but...
他告诉过你了，是不是？
He told you, didn't he?
我离婚了，是个单亲母亲
That I'm divorced and a single mother.
他真是个大嘴巴…
That big mouth of his...
就请拿着吧
Please. Just take it.
我可能没有很多钱
I may not have a lot,
但足以帮帮朋友忙了
but it's enough to help out a friend.
当秉云需要帮忙时，我必须帮他
When Byung-woon needs help, I have to help him.
他帮我度过了很多艰难时光
He helped me through many rough times.
所以就拿着吧
So just take it.
他真的了不起
He's really something.
即使在他情况很差的时候，他还坚持帮助我
He insisted on helping me even when things were worse for him.
你们俩都已经很熟吗？
You two got close, already?
嗨，我很抱歉
Hey, I'm so sorry.
- 刚才我很忙  - 没事
- I was busy before.  - It's okay.
- 我给了她四十万  - 谢谢
- I gave her $400.  - Thanks.
我最好走了
I'd better go.
- 好的  - 很高兴见到你
- Okay.  - Nice meeting you.
- 再见，恩静  - 再见
- See you, Eun-jung.  - Bye.
怎么了？
What?
等等
Wait.
等一下！
Excuse me!
就说已经付钱给我了
Let's say I've already been paid.
请别这样
Don't do this, please.
要是这是因为你考虑到我的情况
If it's 'cuz you're thinking of my state,
那会伤我自尊的
it hurts my pride.
不是，不是那样的
No, please. It's not like that.
我也不能收，我答应过秉云
I can't take it either. I promised Byung-woon.
那…
Then...
咱们这么做，更公平点
Let's do this, to be fair.
- 你不会让步的，是吧？ - 不会
- You won't budge, will you?  - No.
好吧，我输了
Fine. I lose.
秉云？看到了吗？
Byung-woon? See that?
- 我仍旧没食言  - 好的
- I Still kept My promise.  - Okay.
- 好吧，保重  - 再见
- Well, take care.  - Bye.
你为什么那么做？现在我们还差二十万
Why'd you do that? Now we're $200 short.
没事
It's okay.
那很酷，喜秀
That's cool, Hee-su.
- 给我写个欠条  - 什么？
- Write me an IOU.  - What?
- 日后再还我那二十万  - 早就该知道
- Pay me the $200, later.  - Should've known.
- 写呀  - 好的，二十万
- Write it.  - Okay. $200.
加上拖车的八万二
Plus the $82 for towing.
好的
Okay.
鲜花和加油各三万
And $30 each for the flowers and gas.
别这样
Aw, come on.
至少我没算巧克力的钱
At least I'm not charging the chocolates.
但我付大巴和地铁钱了
But I paid for the bus and subway.
那就把它扣掉
Then take that out.
二十万加八万二，加六万…然后…
$200 plus, $82, plus $60... then...
是三十四万二，减去大巴和地铁钱
That's $342 minus the bus and subway fares...
- 我应该把你放哪？ - 嗯？
- Where should I drop you off?  - Huh?
哦，随便哪个地铁站
Oh, any subway station.
你要蒜精吗？我有很多
Want some garlic extract? I got lots.
蒜精有什么用？
What's with garlic extracts?
对女人很好，我给你点
It's really good for women. I'll give you some.
我把你放那行吗？
Should I let you off up there?
可以，好的
That's fine. Okay.
晚饭怎么样？我们还有些时间
How about dinner? We still have some time.
不了，谢谢
No, thanks.
好吧，我也正有约会
Right. I got an appointment, anyways.
给你蒜精
Here's the garlic extract.
你一定要喝呀
Make sure you drink it.
- 你保重  - 再见
- You take care.  - Bye.
免费品尝桑格利亚汽酒，你尝尝吗？
Free taste test for Sangria. Would you like to try some?
你好
Hi there.
是桑格利亚汽酒！
It's Sangria!
桑格利亚汽酒来自西班牙，它易于制造，通过…
Sangria is from Spain, it can be made easily by...
主演：全度妍
JEON Do-youn
你一个人在这吗？
Are you here alone?
主演：河正宇
HA Jung-woo
我很想和你聊聊天
I've been dying to talk to you.
欠条“赵秉云借款三十四万零一百
IOU 'I CHO Byung-woon borrowed $340.10.
我发誓尽快还你”2008年2月16日
I swear to pay you back ASAP. ' February 16th, 2008
导演：李润基
A film by LEE Yoon-ki